Okay, I'm going to go read Myan Dive.
Oh, here it is, the flower path, right?
I'm doing a video of my platform to make sure I'm doing it right.
I'm glad you took it.
Sure thing.
It's totally fine with me.
It happens.
I have this image of the finished product, right?
I think I'm going to be like this, too, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
It's just one time.
Well, okay. You want to take a shot?
I'll take a shot.
You're right.
It's beautiful.
Beautiful.
I don't know. It's beautiful in a different way.
You like the pose?
It's like a bird.
Yeah, it's flapping its wings like a dove.
Maybe it's easier to see from the side.
But I'm just saying it backwards. Look, look, look.
The first time I saw a flower arrangement, look, it's the same.
Don't they look alike?
Yes, they are.
Almost the same.
You get used to it.
You can be like Hanamichi.
I'd like to be able to read this.
Let's read a little more.
Yeah.
That's great. I'm learning a lot.
Like this one, use your knees and relax from the bottom up.
Hmmm, but it sure works.
I do get a little nervous when I shoot.
I have to put a lot of energy into it.
Maybe it's better to relax.
Knees are important. Knees are important.
You want to try using your knees? Like this.
From the bottom up.
That's right.
You want to try this once?
That's good.
Put a lot of pressure on it.
Ooh!
Skill!
It's changing.
Growth!
It says something else.
The way you hold it?
You have to hold your elbow open.
Right hand?
Left hand?
Tighten the left hand side.
And open this one.
Hold it like this.
Like this?
Here we go.
What?
Eyes.
You can use your wrists, too.
Aim the ball at the anti.
Fingers up high.
Okay, okay.
Use your elbows.
Ooh!
Wouldn't you like me to call around a little bit? Don't you want me to call someone around who knows what they're talking about?
You're here.
Get on the phone.
No! What are you talking about?
I'll come in behind you.
I don't know what you're gonna say.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Can I ask you to come to Ibaraki now?
I'm busy.
It's the day before.
The day before.
I'm busy with rehearsals.
Maybe you could drop me a line.
I definitely don't want to.
I don't want to bother him.
You're here, aren't you?
Are you there?
Yes, he's there.
He's the PA who always covers our ears at our shows.
Mr. Takechi.
Mr. Takechi!
Thank you very much.
He is our sound guy.
Thank you very much!
Mr. Takechi, have you played basketball before?
Only three years in junior high.
Oh!
But you're pretty good at it.
It was a long time ago.
I'm a long time old man.
How good are you, Mr. Takechi?
High pressure.
May I? Look at this.
No practice.
Yes, sir.
Is this what you want me to do?
Wow. Wow.
Cute.
Amazing.
Use your knees.
I'll use my knees to do it in front of you.
Like a snack.
Tense bad.
Tense.
Do you hit up front?
Up.
Up and in.
Okay, let's try it.
Oh, wow.
That's good.
Amazing.
Awesome.
Oh!
Ooh.
Ooh
Oh!
Ooh!
Another timing, though.
Crystal's highlight is...
Isn't that the top uppercut?
Yum.
Here you go.
Ooh.
Oh! Ooh.
Oh!
Ooh.
I knew you could rub it in.
Potentially, this is better.
Is that better?
Pawn.
Keysaw.
What are you talking about?
Basics are important.
Okay, guys, not this way.
Up there.
If you can't get in...
This way.
Which way are you going to do it?
If you don't get in.
The first one.
Maybe the second time.
You've already written it.
I threw it once and thought it didn't work.
I'll keep practicing.
I'll start practicing.
Just in case... this way.
This way then.
Just in case.
What about you guys? Then everyone else is.
Only the top.
I'm done.
I was super nervous.
So, that's it.
The house time show is over.